Guide to the Joint Western Area Committee Records, 1965-2004 LAC0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- JWAC May 1977 [4/4], 1977 May; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC July 1977, 1977 July; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Memorandum from Western Master Freight Division regarding procedures, July 6, 1977
- JWAC August 1977 [1/5], 1977 August; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting August 15-19, 1977; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Main Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1977 [2/5], 1977 August; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1977 [3/5], 1977 August; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1977 [4/5], 1977 August; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Main Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC August 1977 [5/5], 1977 August; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC November 1977 [1/4], 1977 November; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting November 14-18, 1977; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1977 [2/4], 1977 November; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1977 [3/4], 1977 November; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  Minutes of Meeting November 14-18, 1977; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee; Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes,Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1977 [4/4], 1977 November; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes
- JWAC February 1978 [1/3], 1978 February; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Minutes Meeting February 14-17, 1978; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries); Proceedings/Transcripts of Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC February 1978 [2/3], 1978 February; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  Transcript/Proceedings of Change of Operations Committee, Joint Council #7 Committee
- JWAC February 1978 [3/3], 1978 February; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Transcript/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee; Minutes of Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, February 13, 1978
- JWAC May 1978 [1/4], 1978 May; LAC0003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Minutes of Meeting May 15-19, 1978, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1978 [2/4], 1978 May; LAC0003 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  Agenda of Meeting May 15-19, 1978; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC May 1978 [3/4], 1978 May; LAC0003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Main Committee; Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1978 [4/4], 1978 May; LAC0003 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Minutes of Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, May 15, 1978, Transcripts/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC August 1978 [1/3], 1978 August; LAC0003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Transcript of Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, August 14, 1978, Transcript/Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1978 [2/3], 1978 August; LAC0003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Meeting August 14-18, 1978; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1978 [3/3], 1978 August; LAC0003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  Transcript/Proceedings of Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC November 1978 [1/2], 1978 November; LAC0003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Main Committee, Change of Operations Committee; Minutes of Meeting November 6-9, 1978, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1978 [2/2], 1978 November; LAC0003 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Transcript/Proceedings of the Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes; Agenda Meeting November 6-10, 1978, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1979 [1/4], 1979 February; LAC0003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee
- JWAC February 1979 [2/4], 1979 February; LAC0003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee; Agenda Meeting February 12-16, 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1979 [3/4], 1979 February; LAC0003 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1979 [4/4], 1979 February; LAC0003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, February 12, 1979; Transcript of Proceedings of Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee; Minutes of Meeting February 12-16, 1979; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1979 [1/2], 1979 May; LAC0003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  Transcript/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee; Agenda Meeting May 14-18, 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1979 [2/2], 1979 May; LAC0003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries); Minutes of Meeting May 14-18, 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1979 [1/3], 1979 August; LAC0003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Minutes of Meeting August 13-17, 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries), Transcript/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations
- JWAC August 1979 [2/3], 1979 August; LAC0003 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  Agenda Meeting August 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC November 1979 [1/4], 1979 November; LAC0003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting November 12-16, 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1979 [2/4], 1979 November; LAC0003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1979 [3/4], 1979 November; LAC0003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1979 [4/4], 1979 November; LAC0003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  Minutes Meeting November 12-16, 1979, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC January 1980, 1980 January; LAC0003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  Report on Action of the Joint Western Area Rider Committee, January 22, 1980
- JWAC February 1980 [1/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting February 11-15, 1980; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1980 [2/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1980 [3/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Minutes of Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, February 11, 1980; Transcript/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC February 1980 [4/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  Minutes of Meeting February 11-15, 1980, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1980 [5/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- JWAC February 1980 [6/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  Proceedings of the Joint Session of the Full and Main Committee
- JWAC February 1980 [7/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1980 [8/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1980 [9/9], 1980 February; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- JWAC April 1980, 1980 April; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  Local Committee Deadlock Decisions
- JWAC May 1980 [1/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  Agenda Meeting May 12-16, 1980; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1980 [2/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1980 [3/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries), Transcripts/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations/Change of Operations
- JWAC May 1980 [4/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Local Operations, Main Committee, May 1980
- JWAC May 1980 [5/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting May 12-16, 1980, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1980 [6/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  Main Committee, Committee for OTR Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1980 [7/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries), Transcript of Proceedings Change of Operations Committee, Main Committee
- JWAC May 1980 [8/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC May 1980 [9/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations
- JWAC May 1980 [10/30], 1980 May; LAC0003 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1980 [11/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 1)
  Transcripts/Proceedings, Main Committee, Sub-Committee on OTR Disputes
- JWAC May 1980 [12/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1980 [13/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1980 [14/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1980 [15/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings, Main Committee, Sub-Committee on OTR Disputes, Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations and Suspensions/ Warning Letters, May 12-15, 1980
- JWAC May 1980 [16/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations and Suspensions/ Warning Letters
- JWAC May 1980 [17/30], 1980 May (Box 30, Folder 7)
- JWAC May 1980 [18/30], 1980 May (Box 31, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1980 [19/30], 1980 May (Box 31, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1980 [20/30], 1980 May (Box 31, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1980 [21/30], 1980 May (Box 31, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations and Suspensions/ Warning Letters, Proceedings of the Joint Session of the Full and Main Committee
- JWAC May 1980 [22/30], 1980 May (Box 31, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Main Committee
- JWAC May 1980 [23/30], 1980 May (Box 31, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1980 [24/30], 1980 May (Box 32, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1980 [25/30], 1980 May (Box 32, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Main Committee; Minutes Meeting May 4-8, 1981; Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1980 [26/30], 1980 May (Box 32, Folder 3)
  Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1980 [27/30], 1980 May (Box 32, Folder 4)
  Committee for Discharges, Terminations and Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries); Transcripts/ Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1980 [28/30], 1980 May (Box 32, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/ Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1980 [29/30], 1980 May (Box 32, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1980 [30/30], 1980 May (Box 33, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1980 [1/20], 1980 August (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Minutes of the Meeting August 11-15, 1980, Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1980 [2/20], 1980 August (Box 33, Folder 3)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Discharges, Terminations and Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1980 [3/20], 1980 August (Box 33, Folder 4)
- JWAC August 1980 [4/20], 1980 August (Box 33, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1980 [5/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1980 [6/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1980 [7/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 3)
  Transcripts/ Proceedings of the Change of Operations and the O-T-R-Committee
- JWAC August 1980 [8/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/ Proceedings of the O-T-R-Committee
- JWAC August 1980 [9/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1980 [10/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations/Jt. Council #7 Disputes (Alternate Main Committee)
- JWAC August 1980 [11/20], 1980 August (Box 34, Folder 7)
- JWAC August 1980 [12/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1980 [13/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 2)
- JWAC August 1980 [14/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 3)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations/Jt. Council #7 Disputes (Alternate Main Committee) and the Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC August 1980 [15/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC August 1980 [16/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1980 [17/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 6)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, Joint Session of the Full and Main Committee, Main Committee Hearings
- JWAC August 1980 [18/20], 1980 August (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Main Committee
- JWAC August 1980 [19/20], 1980 August (Box 36, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1980 [20/20], 1980 August (Box 36, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1980 [1/22], 1980 November (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Minutes Meeting November 3-7, 1980, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1980 [2/22], 1980 November (Box 36, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1980 [3/22], 1980 November (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1980 [4/22], 1980 November (Box 36, Folder 6)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1980 [5/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes
- JWAC November 1980 [6/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Committee for Local Operations and Joint Council #7 Disputes
- JWAC November 1980 [7/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1980 [8/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Joint Session of the Full and Main Committee
- JWAC November 1980 [9/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Main Committee
- JWAC November 1980 [10/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1980 [11/22], 1980 November (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Main Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC November 1980 [12/22], 1980 November (Box 38, Folder 1)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC November 1980 [13/22], 1980 November (Box 38, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1980 [14/22], 1980 November (Box 38, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1980 [15/22], 1980 November (Box 38, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings O-T-R Committee
- JWAC November 1980 [16/22], 1980 November (Box 38, Folder 5)
- JWAC November 1980 [17/22], 1980 November (Box 38, Folder 6)
- JWAC November 1980 [18/22], 1980 November (Box 39, Folder 1)
- JWAC November 1980 [19/22], 1980 November (Box 39, Folder 2)
- JWAC November 1980 [20/22], 1980 November (Box 39, Folder 3)
- JWAC November 1980 [21/22], 1980 November (Box 39, Folder 4)
- JWAC November 1980 [22/22], 1980 November (Box 39, Folder 5)
- JWAC January 1981, 1981 January (Box 39, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1981 [1/25], 1981 February (Box 39, Folder 7)
  Agenda Meeting February 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1981 [2/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 1)
  Main Committee, OTR Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1981 [3/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 2)
  Minutes of Meeting February 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1981 [4/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 3)
  Main Committee, O-T-R Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1981 [5/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 4)
  Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1981 [6/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 5)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC February 1981 [7/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1981 [8/25], 1981 February (Box 40, Folder 7)
- JWAC February 1981 [9/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Agenda, Meeting February 9-13, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, O-T-R Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1981 [10/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1981 [11/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1981 [12/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC February 1981 [13/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1981 [14/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1981 [15/25], 1981 February (Box 41, Folder 7)
- JWAC February 1981 [16/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1981 [17/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1981 [18/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 3)
- JWAC February 1981 [19/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 4)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of the O-T-R Committee
- JWAC February 1981 [20/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 5)
- JWAC February 1981 [21/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 6)
- JWAC February 1981 [22/25], 1981 February (Box 42, Folder 7)
- JWAC February 1981 [23/25], 1981 February (Box 43, Folder 1)
- JWAC February 1981 [24/25], 1981 February (Box 43, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1981 [25/25], 1981 February (Box 43, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1981 [1/22], 1981 May (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Minutes of Meeting of Union Representatives of the JWAC Committee and Representatives of Local Unions, May 4, 1981, Meeting Minutes, May 4-8, 1981, Change of Operations (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1981 [2/22], 1981 May (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes; Main Committee, O-T-R Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1981 [3/22], 1981 May (Box 43, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1981 [4/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1981 [5/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting May 4-8, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1981 [6/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1981 [7/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Committee for Discharges, Committee for Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1981 [8/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 5)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Joint Session of the Full and Main Committee
- JWAC May 1981 [9/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1981 [10/22], 1981 May (Box 44, Folder 7)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1981 [11/22], 1981 May (Box 45, Folder 1)
- JWAC May 1981 [12/22], 1981 May (Box 45, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1981 [13/22], 1981 May (Box 45, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1981 [14/22], 1981 May (Box 45, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes
- JWAC May 1981 [15/22], 1981 May (Box 45, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1981 [16/22], 1981 May (Box 45, Folder 6)
- JWAC May 1981 [17/22], 1981 May (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the O-T-R Committee
- JWAC May 1981 [18/22], 1981 May (Box 46, Folder 2)
- JWAC May 1981 [19/22], 1981 May (Box 46, Folder 3)
- JWAC May 1981 [20/22], 1981 May (Box 46, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters
- JWAC May 1981 [21/22], 1981 May (Box 46, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1981 [22/22], 1981 May (Box 47, Folder 1)
- JWAC August 1981 [1/34], 1981 August (Box 47, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting August 10-15, 1981, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, Main Sub-Committee (OTR Disputes), Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [2/34], 1981 August (Box 47, Folder 3)
  Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [3/34], 1981 August (Box 47, Folder 4)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee, OTR Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [4/34], 1981 August (Box 47, Folder 5)
- JWAC August 1981 [5/34], 1981 August (Box 47, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting August 10-15, 1981, Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries), Minutes of Meeting of Union Representatives of the JWAC Committee and Representatives of Local Unions, August 10, 1981
- JWAC August 1981 [6/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 1)
  Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [7/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 2)
  Committee for O-T-R Disputes, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1981 [8/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 3)
- JWAC August 1981 [9/34], 1981 August (Box 48, Folder 4)